<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bryant Property Management, LLC.</title>
    <link>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bryant Property Management, LLC.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 15:41:39 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>2708 Hollins Ferry Road Apt. A</title>
      <link>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/properties/2708-hollins-ferry-road-apt-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 15:41:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/properties/2708-hollins-ferry-road-apt-a/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3625 Everett Street</title>
      <link>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/properties/3625-everett-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 15:41:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/properties/3625-everett-street/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biographies</title>
      <link>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/biographies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 14:05:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/biographies/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mark-bryant:41dcca77656c2fe8e9bff80bf5a32892&#34;&gt;Mark Bryant&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;founder-resident-agent-financial-analyst-and-repairs:41dcca77656c2fe8e9bff80bf5a32892&#34;&gt;Founder, Resident Agent, Financial Analyst and Repairs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Bryant began learning skills in carpentry and construction when he was employed by Fick Bros Roofing &amp;amp; Exterior Remodeling Company. His skill set varies to include plumbing, electrical and wood working. Aside from being a partner CEO and founder of Bryant Property Management, LLC., he is also the main repair person at the company. In his spare time, he enjoys tinkering with things around the house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;cathy-bryant:41dcca77656c2fe8e9bff80bf5a32892&#34;&gt;Cathy Bryant&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;founder-managing-member-customer-relations-and-repairs:41dcca77656c2fe8e9bff80bf5a32892&#34;&gt;Founder, Managing Member, Customer Relations and Repairs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early in her life, Cathy Bryant worked retail and customer service where she learned how to maneuver within an office setting and communicate with clients. She has been the heart of Bryant Property Management, LLC. headquarters for many years; Cathy has balanced office work with assisting her husband and business partner, Mark, with repairs. When not working, she is giving back to the community by raising cancer awareness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;andrew-bryant:41dcca77656c2fe8e9bff80bf5a32892&#34;&gt;Andrew Bryant&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;technical-support-financial-analyst-and-repairs:41dcca77656c2fe8e9bff80bf5a32892&#34;&gt;Technical Support, Financial Analyst, and Repairs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2013 their son, Andrew, joined the family business and has updated and maintained the company&amp;rsquo;s computer infrastructure. He also helps with repairs when needed and ensures Bryant Property Management&amp;rsquo;s network is working on all levels. Outside of the company he is always reading about new technologies and how technology can benefit the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Company History</title>
      <link>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/company-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 14:05:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/company-history/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bryant Property Management, LLC. has been a family owned and operated business since 1987 and became an LLC in 2004. It began with Mark and Cathy Bryant, Co-owners and CEOs, starting their rental business in Baltimore and has since expanded into the Glen Burnie area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bryant Property Management, LLC. assists a wide range of families. The company has worked closely with Housing Commission of Anne Arundel County (section 8) or also known as HCAAC for over 16 years to provide housing options for those who need assistance. In recent times, we have expanded to work with other agencies in the area including People Encouraging People (PEP) and Housing Commission of Annapolis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the company has expanded the number of properties managed, Bryant Property Management, LLC remains family owned operated.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission Statement</title>
      <link>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/mission-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 14:05:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/mission-statement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bryant Property Management aims to provide quality homes and equal housing opportunities to the Baltimore-Glen Burnie area. We stride to ensure that everything in the homes are in working condition at all times. One of the things we say is &amp;ldquo;if we can&amp;rsquo;t live in them ourselves then we won&amp;rsquo;t give out the keys for someone else too&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision Statement</title>
      <link>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/vision-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 14:05:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bryantpropertymgmt.biz/about/vision-statement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To make it possible for families to have a place to call home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>